Human Rights Watch records: Record Group 4: Africa Watch 7746709
Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series 1: Karen Sorensen, 1979-1996
  - Subseries I.2: Country Files, 1979-1995
    - Cameroon
      - Ghana
        - Lawyers Committee--Case File, 1991 (Box 238, Folder 25)
        - Press Clippings, 1989-1992; (2 Folders) (Box 238, Folder 26 to 27)
        - Reports, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 28)
        - The Stolen Verdict: Ghana Presidentia Election Presidential Election, 1992 November (Box 238, Folder 29)
        - Student/Academic Abuses, 1981-1992 (Box 238, Folder 30)
      - Guinea--Press Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Guinea-Bissau
        - Amnesty International, 1993 (Box 239, Folder 2)
        - Press Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Ivory Coast
        - Academic Freedom
          - Contacts, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 4)
          - General, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 5)
          - Ligue Ivoirienne des droits de l'homme, (LIDHO), 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 6)
          - Opposition Papers, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 7)
          - Reports, 1986-1990 (Box 239, Folder 8)
          - Rough Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 239, Folder 9)
          - Students, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 10)
        - Basilica, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 11)
        - Cote D'Ivoire, 1991 (Box 239, Folder 12)
        - Elections and Politics, 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 13)
        - Media, 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 14)
        - Non-Student Protests and Unrest, 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 15)
        - Press Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 239, Folder 16)
        - Africa Watch, 1991-1992 (Box 240, Folder 1)
        - Background Information, 1992-1993 (Box 240, Folder 2)
        - Clashes, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 3)
        - Contacts, 1988 (Box 240, Folder 4)
        - Economy/Aid, 1991-1994 (Box 240, Folder 5)
        - Ethnic Clashes, 1992 (Box 240, Folder 6)
        - Forcible Return of Somali Refugees Government Repression of Kenyan Somalis, 1989 (Box 240, Folder 7)
        - Freedom of Expression, 1992-1994 (Box 240, Folder 8)
        - General Correspondence, 1988-1993; (4 Folders) (Box 240, Folder 9 to 12)
        - General Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 240, Folder 13)
        - Human Rights Groups--Outside, 1991-1992 (Box 240, Folder 14)
        - Imanyara, Gitobu1990 (Box 240, Folder 15)
        - Islamic Party of Kenya (IPK), 1993 (Box 240, Folder 16)
        - Materials
          - Inside Country, 1991-1992 (Box 240, Folder 17)
          - Western Governments, 1991-1992 (Box 240, Folder 18)
        - Press Clippings, 1985-1987, 1989-1992, (5 Folders) (Box 240, Folder 19 to 23)
        - Press Clippings, 1991-1994; (5 Folders) (Box 241, Folder 1 to 5)
        - Refugees, 1992-1994 (Box 241, Folder 6)
        - Reports, 1988-1990, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 241, Folder 7 to 8)
        - Telexes, 1988-1989 (Box 241, Folder 9)
        - United States Policy, 1992-1994 (Box 241, Folder 10)
        - Weekly Review, 1992 (Box 241, Folder 11)
        - Women, 1992 (Box 241, Folder 12)
      - Lesotho Press Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 241, Folder 13)
      - Liberia
        - About Liberia, 1986-1988 (Box 241, Folder 14)
        - African Church, 1987-1989 (Box 241, Folder 15)
        - Americas Watch, 1985-1986 (Box 241, Folder 16)
        - Association for Constitutional Democracy in Liberia (ACDL), 1987-1989 (Box 241, Folder 17)
        - Clips, 1985-1988, 1990, 1993 (Box 241, Folder 18 to 20)
        - Congress--United States, 1986-1987 (Box 241, Folder 21)
        - Constitution., Undated (Box 242, Folder 1)
        - Daily Observer--Press Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 242, Folder 2)
        - Detainees--Curtis Williams and James Bush, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 3)
        - Dunele, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 4)
        - Economy, 1987-1988 (Box 242, Folder 5)
        - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 242, Folder 6)
        - Friends of Liberia, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 7)
        - General, undated (Box 242, Folder 8)
        - Generalized System of Preferences--Petitions, 1988-1989 (Box 242, Folder 9)
          [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2065]
        - Hearings before Africa Subcommittees, 1986 (Box 242, Folder 10)
        - Human Rights--Victims, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 11)
        - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1990 (Box 242, Folder 12)
        - International Human Rights Law Group, 1986 (Box 242, Folder 13)
        - Liberia: a Country Study, 1982 (Box 242, Folder 14)
        - Liberia Alert, 1985-1986 (Box 242, Folder 15)
        - Liberia Update, 1988-1989 (Box 242, Folder 16)
        - Liberian Studies Association, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 17)
        - National Patriotic Front, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 18)
        - Political Parties and Elections, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 19)
        - Politics, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 20)
        - Sirleaf, Ellen Johnson--economist, 1985-1986 (Box 242, Folder 21)
      - Madagascar--Press Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 242, Folder 22)
      - Malawi
        - Amnesty International, 1993 (Box 242, Folder 23)
        - Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 242, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence--General, 1990-1992 (Box 242, Folder 25)
        - General, 1989-1992 (Box 242, Folder 26)
        - General--Africa Watch, 1991-1992 (Box 242, Folder 27)
        - Human Rights Groups--External, 1992 (Box 242, Folder 28)
        - Material from inside country, 1992 (Box 242, Folder 29)
        - Western Governments, 1992 (Box 242, Folder 30)
      - Mali Press--Press Clippings and Reports, 1989-1992; (4 Folders) (Box 242, Folder 31 to 34)
      - Mauritania--Press Clippings and Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 242, Folder 35)
      - Mauritius--Press Clippings, 1988-1991 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Morocco--Press Clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Mozambique
        - Amnesty International, 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 243, Folder 3)
        - Articles, 1989-1990, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Background, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 6)
        - Catholic Church, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 7)
        - Center for Strategic & International Studies, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 8)
        - Clippings and Press, 1984-1992; (3 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 9 to 11)
        - Conference on Emergency Assistance to Mozambique--Photo Exhibit, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 243, Folder 13)
        - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 243, Folder 14)
        - Gersony, Robert Summary of Mozambican Refugee Accounts of Principally Conflict-Related Experience in Mozambique, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 15)
        - International Committee of the Red Cross, 1987-1988 (Box 243, Folder 16)
        - Mozambique Information Office, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 243, Folder 17)
        - Mozambique Ministry of Health, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 18)
        - Mozambique Relief and Refugee Agencies, 1986-1988 (Box 243, Folder 19)
        - Mozambique Research Center, 1987-1988 (Box 243, Folder 20)
        - RENAMO (Mozambique National Resistance), 1987-1988 (Box 243, Folder 21)
        - United Nations--The Emergency Situation in Mozambique, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 22)
        - United States Committee for Refugees, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 23)
      - Namibia
        - General, 1985, 1988-1992, (3 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 24 to 26)
        - Press Clippings, 1988-1990; (3 Folders) (Box 243, Folder 27 to 29)
        - Articles, 1988, 1992 (Box 244, Folder 1)
        - Development Institute, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 2)
        - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 244, Folder 3)
        - General, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 4)
        - Laws and Constitution, undated (Box 244, Folder 5)
        - Laws--United States, 1985, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 6)
        - Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law, 1989-1990 (Box 244, Folder 7)
        - Lutheran World Federation, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 8)
        - Monitors, 1989-1990 (Box 244, Folder 9)
        - Namibia Information Service, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 10)
        - Police, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 11)
        - Press, 1986-1988 (Box 244, Folder 12)
        - SWAPO and Nujoma, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 13)
        - United Nations, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 14)
      - Niger--Press Clippings, 1990-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 15 to 16)
      - Nigeria
        - Academic Freedom, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 17)
        - Active Cases, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 18)
        - African Commission on Human and Peoples Rights, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 19)
        - African nations--involvement with, 1990-1994 (Box 244, Folder 20)
        - AIDS, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 21)
        - Akinseye-George, Yemi--Researcher, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 22)
        - Alliance for Democracy, 1992 (Box 244, Folder 23)
        - Amnesty International, 1989-1992, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 24)
        - Arts, 1989-1991 (Box 244, Folder 25)
        - Babangida, Ibrahim (military ruler), 1990-1993; (3 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 26 to 28)
        - Babangida, Maryam, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 29)
        - Books, 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 30)
        - Britain, 1989-1993 (Box 244, Folder 31)
        - Bush Report, 1991-1992; (2 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 32 to 33)
        - Cameroon--relations with, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 34)
        - Campaign for Democracy, 1992-1993 (Box 244, Folder 35)
        - Children, 1991-1992 (Box 244, Folder 36)
        - Civil Liberties Organisation, 1988-1995; (5 Folders) (Box 244, Folder 37 to 41)
        - Civil Liberties Organisation--Journal of Human Rights Law and Practice, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 42)
        - Immigration, 1990-1991 (Box 244, Folder 43)
        - Political Asylum, 1990 (Box 244, Folder 44)
        - Committee for the Defense of Human Rights, 1989-1995; (3 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Constitution, 1990 (Box 245, Folder 4)
        - Constitutional Rights Project, 1990-1995 (Box 245, Folder 5)
        - Constitutional Rights Project--Constitutional Rights News, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 6)
        - Correspondence
          - Abacha, Sani, 1993 (Box 245, Folder 7)
          - Africa Watch to Nigerian Government, 1992-1993 (Box 245, Folder 8)
          - An-Na'im, Abdullahi, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 9)
          - Moose, George, 1993 (Box 245, Folder 10)
          - Omaar, Rakiya, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 11)
          - Sorensen, Karen, 1991-1994; (4 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 12 to 15)
        - Corruption, 1990-1995 (Box 245, Folder 16)
        - Coups, 1990-1991 (Box 245, Folder 17)
        - Crow, Melissa--Mission, 1995 (Box 245, Folder 18)
        - Death Penalty, 1990 (Box 245, Folder 19)
        - Debt, 1991-1992 (Box 245, Folder 20)
        - Decrees--General, 1991, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 21)
        - Decrees--Decree 2, 1989-1991 (Box 245, Folder 22)
        - Democratic Alternative, 1994 (Box 245, Folder 23)
        - Democratization, 1989-1991; (4 Folders) (Box 245, Folder 24 to 27)
        - Demonstrations, 1989-1991 (Box 246, Folder 1)
        - Deportations, 1988 (Box 246, Folder 2)
        - Detentions, 1989-1990 (Box 246, Folder 3)
        - Development, 1990-1992 (Box 246, Folder 4)
        - Diamond, Larry--Articles, 1991 (Box 246, Folder 5)
        - Drugs, 1990-1995 (Box 246, Folder 6)
        - Ebibillo, Tony--Deportation, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 7)
        - Economy, 1990-1994; (2 Folders) (Box 246, Folder 8 to 9)
        - Election Annulled, 1993; (2 Folders) (Box 246, Folder 10 to 11)
        - Environment, 1989-1992 (Box 246, Folder 12)
        - Ethnic Conflict, 1992-1994 (Box 246, Folder 13)
        - Executions, 1990 (Box 246, Folder 14)
        - Fawehinmi, Gani--human rights lawyer, 1989, 1992 (Box 246, Folder 15)
        - Government, 1989-1993 (Box 246, Folder 16)
        - Health, 1990-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 246, Folder 17)
        - Hijacking, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 18)
        - History, 1990 (Box 246, Folder 19)
        - Hoover Institution Conference, 1990
          - Papers, (3 Folders) (Box 246, Folder 20 to 22)
          - Programs and Summary (Box 246, Folder 23)
        - Human Rights Africa, 1990-1991 (Box 246, Folder 24)
        - Human Rights and the Administration Of Criminal Justice, 1991 (Box 247, Folder 1)
        - Human Rights--General, 1989-1994; (3 Folders) (Box 247, Folder 2 to 4)
        - Human Rights Monitor, 1995 (Box 247, Folder 5)
        - Immigration, 1990 (Box 247, Folder 6)
        - Industrial Outlook for Petroleum and Natural Gas, 1991 (Box 247, Folder 7)
        - Internal Conflicts, 1990-1991 (Box 247, Folder 8)
        - International Relations, 1990-1995 (Box 247, Folder 9)
        - International Seminar on Human Rights, 1992 (Box 247, Folder 10)
        - Judiciary, 1990-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 247, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Jukun-Tiv Conflict, 1992-1993 (Box 247, Folder 13)
          [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2069]
        - Kaduna
          - General, 1991-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 247, Folder 14 to 15)
          - Kaduna Riots, 1992 (Box 247, Folder 16)
        - Kuti, Fela--musician and human rights activist, 1989-1990 (Box 247, Folder 17)
        - Labor, 1989-1995; (2 Folders) (Box 247, Folder 18 to 19)
        - Lagos Riots, 1992 (Box 247, Folder 20)
        - Land, 1990-1992 (Box 247, Folder 21)
        - Language, 1993 (Box 247, Folder 22)
        - Law, 1978, 1984, 1989 (Box 247, Folder 23)
        - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 247, Folder 24)
        - Legal, 1994 (Box 247, Folder 25)
        - Letter--Introduction, 1992 (Box 247, Folder 26)
        - Liberia--1990-1991 (Box 247, Folder 27)
        - Lynching, undated (Box 247, Folder 28)
        - Military, 1990-1993 (Box 247, Folder 29)
        - Minorities, 1990-1993 (Box 247, Folder 30)
        - National Association of Democratic Lawyers, 1990-1992 (Box 247, Folder 31)
        - National Democratic Coalition, 1994 (Box 247, Folder 32)
        - Press
          - Articles, 1989-1994 (Box 247, Folder 33)
          - Freedom, 1989 (Box 247, Folder 34)
        - National Forum, 1990 (Box 248, Folder 1)
        - National Guard, 1990-1993 (Box 248, Folder 2)
        - New Nigerian Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 248, Folder 3)
        - Nigerian Roundtable, 1994 (Box 248, Folder 4)
        - Musa, Alhaji Balarabe, 1989 (Box 248, Folder 5)
        - Obstacles to Justice, 1992 (Box 248, Folder 6)
        - Ogoni people, 1986, 1993-1995 (Box 248, Folder 7)
        - Oil, 1992-1995 (Box 248, Folder 8)
        - On the Eve of Change, A Transition to What?--Press Release, 1991 (Box 248, Folder 9)
        - Open Ballot, 1990 (Box 248, Folder 10)
        - Police, 1987-1994; (2 Folders) (Box 248, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Police Abuses, 1988-1991 (Box 248, Folder 13)
        - Politics, 1994 January-1994 August; (8 Folders) (Box 248, Folder 14 to 21)
        - Politics, 1994 September-1995, (6 Folders) (Box 249, Folder 1 to 6)
        - Population, 1990-1992 (Box 249, Folder 7)
        - Press Clippings, 1987-1995; (3 Folders) (Box 249, Folder 8 to 10)
        - Prisons, 1989-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 249, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Pro-Democracy Groups, 1992 (Box 249, Folder 13)
        - Publications miscellaneous, 1986, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 249, Folder 14)
        - Refugees--deportations, 1990-1992 (Box 249, Folder 15)
        - Regionalism, 1990-1991 (Box 249, Folder 16)
        - Religion, 1990-1994; (3 Folders) (Box 249, Folder 17-19)
        - Religion--Correspondence (Box 249, Folder 20)
        - Relocations, 1990 (Box 249, Folder 21)
        - Research Resumes, 1991 (Box 249, Folder 22)
        - Rural Development, 1989-1990 (Box 249, Folder 23)
        - Shell International Petroleum Company Ltd., 1994-1995 (Box 250, Folder 1)
        - Solaring, Dr. Tai, 1989-1990 (Box 250, Folder 2)
        - Soyinka, Wole, 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 250, Folder 3)
        - Students, 1989-1995; (6 Folders) (Box 250, Folder 4 to 9)
        - Trade, 1990 (Box 250, Folder 10)
        - Traditional Rule, 1991 (Box 250, Folder 11)
        - Transition, 1992-July 1993; (4 Folders) (Box 250, Folder 12 to 15)
        - Transition, 1993 August-1993 December; (8 Folders) (Box 251, Folder 1 to 8)
        - United Kingdom, 1994 (Box 251, Folder 9)
        - United Nations, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 251, Folder 10)
        - United States
          - General, 1987-1991, 1993 (Box 251, Folder 11)
          - Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 251, Folder 12)
        - Universal Defenders of Democracy, 1993 (Box 251, Folder 13)
        - West Africa, 1993 (Box 251, Folder 14)
        - Women, 1990-1994; (2 Folders) (Box 251, Folder 15 to 16)
        - World Report, 1992 (Box 251, Folder 17)
        - Writers, 1991-1993 (Box 251, Folder 18)
      - Rwanda
        - Africa Watch, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 1)
        - Amnesty International
          - Burundi, 1994 (Box 252, Folder 2)
          - Urgent Action Letters, 1990-1994 (Box 252, Folder 3)
        - Articles, 1992 (Box 252, Folder 4)
        - Association of Banyarwanda-Rwandese Patriotic Front, 1990-1991 (Box 252, Folder 5)
        - Background, 1990-1991 (Box 252, Folder 6)
        - Burundi, 1992 (Box 252, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence
          - Africa Watch, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 8)
          - General, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 9)
          - Jefferson, Nicola, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 10)
          - Rwandan Government, 1990-1992 (Box 252, Folder 11)
        - Ethnic Problems, 1991 (Box 252, Folder 12)
        - General, 1989-1992; (5 Folders) (Box 252, Folder 13 to 17)
        - Human Rights Organizations
          - European, 1990-1991 (Box 252, Folder 18)
          - General, 1992 (Box 252, Folder 19)
          - Local, 1990-1991 (Box 252, Folder 20)
        - Interviews, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 1988-1992; (2 Folders) (Box 253, Folder 2 to 3)
        - Mission, 1991
          - Materials, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 4)
          - Testimonies, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 5)
        - Missionaries, 1990-1991 (Box 253, Folder 6)
        - Newspapers, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 7)
        - Obstacles to Justice--materials, 1992 (Box 253, Folder 8)
        - Official Documents, 1984-1991 (Box 253, Folder 9)
        - Political Parties, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 10)
        - Press and Journalists, 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 11)
        - Running File, 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 12)
        - Tutsi businessman, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 13)
        - Victims of Political Repression, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 14)
        - World Bank and International Monetary Fund (IMF), 1991 (Box 253, Folder 15)
      - Senegal--Reports, 1989-1993; (3 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 1 to 3)
      - Sierra Leone--Press Clippings, 1989-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Somalia
        - Africa Watch, 1988-1992 (Box 254, Folder 6)
        - Aid Agencies, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 7)
        - Amnesty International, 1988-1990, 1993 (Box 254, Folder 8)
        - Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 9)
        - Ceasefire, 1992 (Box 254, Folder 10)
        - Congress United States, 1988 (Box 254, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1992; (2 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 12 to 13)
        - Foreign Broadcast Information Service (FBIS)--Daily Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 254, Folder 14)
        - Human Rights Groups, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 15)
        - Press Clippings, 1984, 1988-1991, (5 Folders) (Box 254, Folder 16 to 20)
        - Press Clippings, 1991-1992; (10 Folders) (Box 255, Folder 1 to 10)
        - Testimonies, 1988-1990 (Box 255, Folder 11)
        - Somali National Movement, 1988 (Box 256, Folder 1)
        - Somaliland, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 2)
        - United Nations, 1992 (Box 256, Folder 3)
        - United States
          - Human Rights Watch, 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 4)
          - Somali Political Situation
            - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 256, Folder 5)
            - Reports, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 6)
        - Western Governments, 1990-1992 (Box 256, Folder 7)
      - South Africa
        - Press Clippings, 1982-1989; (8 Folders) (Box 256, Folder 8 to 15)
        - Press Clippings, 1990 January-1991 May; (16 Folders) (Box 257, Folder 1 to 16)
        - Press Clippings, 1991 June-1991 December; (7 Folders) (Box 258, Folder 1 to 7)
      - Sudan
        - Amnesty International, 1993 (Box 258, Folder 8)
        - Press Clippings and Reports, 1991-1993; (2 Folders) (Box 258, Folder 9 to 10)
      - Swaziland
        - Articles, 1992 (Box 258, Folder 11)
        - Human Rights Groups, 1991 (Box 258, Folder 12)
        - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 258, Folder 13)
      - Tanzania
        - Africa Watch, 1989-1991 (Box 258, Folder 14)
        - Africa Watch, 1989-1991 (Box 258, Folder 14a)
        - Articles, 1992 (Box 258, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 258, Folder 16)
        - Human Rights Groups, 1991 (Box 258, Folder 17)
        - Laws, 1984, 1992 (Box 258, Folder 18)
        - The Liberty Desk, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 19)
        - The Liberty Desk, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 19a)
        - Press Clippings, 1989-1994; (2 Folders) (Box 258, Folder 20 to 21)
      - Togo
        - Academic Events
          - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 22)
          - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 258, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 258, Folder 24)
        - Courrier du Golfe, 1992-1993 (Box 258, Folder 25)
        - Democratization, 1993 (Box 258, Folder 26)
        - Human Rights--Violations
          - General, 1992-1993 (Box 258, Folder 27)
          - Journalists, 1991-1993 (Box 258, Folder 28)
          - Lists of Organizations, 1993 (Box 258, Folder 29)
        - Laws, 1966-1988 (Box 258, Folder 30)
        - Obstacles to Justice--General, 1988 (Box 258, Folder 31)
        - Political Crisis
          - Elections, 1992-1993 (Box 258, Folder 32)
          - Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box 258, Folder 33)
          - Press, 1992-1993 (Box 258, Folder 34)
          - Press, 1992-1993 (Box 258, Folder 34a)
          - Press Clippings, 1985-1993; (7 Folders) (Box 259, Folder 1 to 7)
          - Reports, 1988, 1991-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 259, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Tunisia-Press Clippings, 1989, 1991 (Box 259, Folder 10)
      - Uganda
        - Articles and Wires, 1992 (Box 259, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1988-1992; (2 Folders) (Box 259, Folder 12 to 13)
        - Human Rights Draft Constitution, 1993 October (Box 259, Folder 14)
        - Human Rights Groups--Outside, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 15)
        - Laws--Background, 1991 (Box 259, Folder 16)
        - Material
          - Inside Country, 1991 (Box 259, Folder 17)
          - Western Governments, 1991 (Box 259, Folder 18)
        - Press Clippings, 1990-1993; (4 Folders) (Box 260, Folder 1 to 4)
        - U.S. Committee for Refugees--Issue Brief, 1990 February (Box 260, Folder 5)
      - Zaire
        - Africa Faith and Justice Network (AFJN), 1992 (Box 260, Folder 6)
        - Amnesty International, 1993 (Box 260, Folder 7)
        - AMOS--Mpundu, Jose, 1990-1992 (Box 260, Folder 8)
        - Articles and Wires, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 9)
        - Association Zairoise de Defense des droits de l'homme, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 10)
        - Broadcast Journalists, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1989-1992 (Box 260, Folder 12)
          - Policy, 1983, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 260, Folder 13)
        - Droits de l'homme, maintenant, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 14)
        - Human Rights Groups
          - Other, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 15)
          - Outside (Box 260, Folder 16)
        - Ligue Zairoise des droits de l'homme
          - Documents, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 17)
          - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 18)
          - Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 19)
          - Tribune des Libertes, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 20)
        - National Committee, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 21)